theknicksblog.com 2018-01-27

# Privacy policy | SNY

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE OR ANY OTHER SPORTSNET NEW YORK PRODUCT OR SERVICE.**

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**  
1\. General  
2\. Information Automatically Collected; Cookies; Web Beacons  
3\. Our Security Practices  
4\. How You Can Review Your Personal Information  
5\. Choice  
6\. Links  
7\. Special Rules for Children  
8\. Parental Consent  
9\. Contact Us; Privacy Administrator  
10\. Notification of Changes

**General**  
Sterling Entertainment Enterprises, LLC, d/b/a SportsNet New York ("SNY"), in association with MLB Advanced Media, L.P. ("MLBAM"), produces http://sny.tv/, the Official Website of SportsNet New York (this "Website"). We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Website.

You can visit and enjoy this Website without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, we offer some special services, and for these services to work properly we will need you to share with us certain personal information about yourself. The personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to, full name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number(s) (e.g., home, work, mobile and/or fax) and birth date. We may also collect other personal information that will be identified on applicable page(s) of this Website. If you submit any personal information to us, or to any third-party service providers acting on our behalf, you can be assured that we will not sell, lease, or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as follows: (1) to those third-party service providers, and only so that they may help us provide services you've requested and in certain circumstances to provide you with special offers; (2) upon notice posted on an applicable location of this Website where we collect your personal information for an economic transaction and notify you that we will be sharing such information with a third party, where such third party is clearly identified; and (3) on occasion, we may offer a special promotion (such as a sweepstakes, contest, fantasy game or free subscription to goods and/or services) on this Website in conjunction with a third-party service provider, sponsor, or promotional partner, and share your information with that service provider, sponsor, or promotional partner so that it can send you other special promotions it offers, but only if you give us permission to do so.

**Special Offers and Promotions.**  
With your permission, we may also send you e-mails with special offers and promotions. If you don't want to receive these, you may change your preferences by accessing the "Newsletters" section within your Website account.

**Information Automatically Collected; Cookies; Web Beacons**  
We may use automatic methods such as cookies (small amounts of data, which often include an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive), single-pixel GIF images ("web beacons") or similar technologies, alone or in combination with personally identifiable information you choose to provide us, to make this Website work better, to understand Website usage and trends, to deliver a more personalized experience and to improve the content and offerings of this Website. Examples of the information we collect and analyze using such methods include, without limitation, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; e-mail address; login name and password; operating system type, version and computer platform; purchase history, which we may aggregate with similar information from other customers; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, on, and from this Website, including date and time; cookie information; and products you viewed or searched for. We may also use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs) and methods used to browse away from the page.

We may also use cookies to enable you to use a "shopping cart" if you want to purchase goods or services while on this Website, and to offer you products, programs, or services based on purchase and Website usage behavior that you and/or other customers have exhibited. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to accept or reject cookies. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain services on this Website.

We do not transfer cookies associated with this Website to any other company, nor do we authorize any other company to access the cookies we have placed on your computer's hard drive. We may allow other companies that are presenting advertisements or providing services on the pages of this Website to set and access cookies on your computer and/or web beacons or similar technologies on certain of those pages and/or certain emails sent by us.

**About our ads:** Many advertisements are managed and placed on this Website by third parties. These companies are called "network advertisers." Network advertisers who place advertisements on this Website may use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this Website and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like to obtain more information about this common industry practice of network advertisers and to make choices about their use of your information, please [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp#)

We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with this Website, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. "Spyware" or "adware" is any software which has been downloaded to and/or installed on an Internet user's computer, without the user's actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred.

****Aggregated Demographic Information.****  
We may share aggregated demographic information with third parties, but this information is not linked to any personal information that can identify you or another individual person. Therefore, no personal information is disclosed in this manner.

****Business Transfers.****  
As time passes, SNY, the owner of any information collected from this Website, may be sold along with its respective assets, or other transactions may occur in which customer information is one of the business assets transferred. In such a case, the customer information which has been gathered from this Website may be one of the business assets transferred by SNY.

****Disclosure for Legal Purposes.****  
SNY, the owner of any information collected from this Website, may be required to share your personal information and non-personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants, or orders. If SNY is required to do so, it will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, SNY reserves the right to use, disclose, and/or share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Website's Terms of Use or as otherwise required by law.

****Our Security Practices****  
Your Website account preferences are password protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas, we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

****How You Can Review Your Personal Information****  
If you want to review or revise the personal information you provided during registration on this Website, and whether you want to receive communications from us, you can either (1) [click here to log in](https://www.sny.tv/sign-in), and then click on the "My Account" option on the top left side of the page, or (2) contact SNY.tv, Privacy Administrator c/o MLBAM, 75 Ninth Avenue, New York, New York 10011 Phone: (212) 485-4500 Fax: (212) 485-8989; or send an e-mail to [legal@comcastsportsnet.com](mailto:legal@comcastsportsnet.com). If you want to close your account with us and have us delete the personal information in it (except for information that we keep for record-keeping purposes), you should contact [legal@comcastsportsnet.com](mailto:legal@comcastsportsnet.com).

****Choice****  
Our registration and order forms contain a box for you to indicate whether or not you consent to receive special offers and promotions from us and/or our partners. Unless you give us your consent to use your personal information for these purposes, we and our partners will only use it to complete the transaction or provide the service or product you have requested. If you indicate that you consent to receive communications or solicitations, but you later change your mind, you can revise your preferences by accessing the "Newsletters" section within your Website account.

****Links****  
Our Website contains links to other Websites produced by MLB Advanced Media, L.P. and to Websites operated by unrelated third parties. In addition, if you click on an advertisement on this Website, you may be directed to a web page within this Website or to a third- party Website. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party Websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when your leave this Website and to read the privacy policies of every Website that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website. ****

****Special Rules For Children****  
Because of federal law, we cannot knowingly collect any personal information from a child under the age of thirteen without the consent of that child's parent. The statements in this Privacy Policy generally about our collection and use of personal information also apply to our treatment of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, with the added protection of the special "Parental Consent" rules that follow. Some services on this Website (e.g., NY Team Shop) require the submission of a credit card number along with personal information in connection with a purchase, and are therefore not available to children without their parent's consent. Other services on this Website are not available to children under the age of thirteen. If a child who SNY knows to be under the age of thirteen attempts to utilize a service on this Website which is not available to children, he/she will receive a message which states "You are not eligible" for the service.

****Parental Consent****  
Parents who are interested in services that are available to children under the age of thirteen should [contact this Website's Privacy Administrator](https://www.sny.tv/contact-us) for a consent form. The consent form will include a notice describing this Privacy Policy and will ask for the parent's consent to our collection and use of personal information from or about their child. If the consent form is not completed by the parent and not returned to this Website's Privacy Administrator, the child will not be able to access those activities requiring registration and we will not collect any personal information from that child. A child's parent has the option to consent to our collection and use of their child's personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to third parties, but if such disclosure is necessary to make available a service which has been requested, then the child will not have access to such service.

****Information Collected****  
Depending on the special service requested, personal information collected may include a full name, email address, street address, or age of a child. We will not condition a child's participation in any activity on this Website on the child's disclosing more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity.

If a parent has consented to our collection of personal information about his/her child, the parent can review his/her child's personal information by accessing the child's Website account. A parent can instruct us to delete the child's personal information or to stop collecting or using the child's personal information by [contacting the Privacy Administrator](https://www.sny.tv/contact-us).

****Information Use****  
We may use the personal information we collect to provide the child with the special services for which he or she has registered, as well as for fulfilling a requested transaction, record keeping, or marketing back to the child. Please note that when anyone, including a child, uses a message board or chat room on this Website, the communications are publicly available to the other participants.

****Information Disclosure****  
After obtaining the consent of the child's parent, we, our service providers, and SportsNet New York, will maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information collected about the child. A child's information will only be disclosed to our third-party service providers and SportsNet New York as described in this Privacy Policy. The following are third-party service providers that may collect or maintain personal information from children under thirteen on our behalf: Pluck (message boards, comments). These third-party service providers cannot use your child's personal information without your consent for any purpose other than the service you've requested on behalf of your child.

****Contact Us****  
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: [legal@comcastsportsnet.com](mailto:legal@comcastsportsnet.com).

****Notification of Changes****  
If we make an important change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link on the homepage of this Website so that you can review the updated policy.

LAST UPATED: July 20, 2010
